Why did it end like that?
なんでそんな終わってんの?
What's interesting?
何が面白い?
Can you tell me?
言ってもらえん?
face?
顔?
Whose face is interesting?
誰の顔が面白いんだよ
You know, there's a side effect.
このね、副面が
surely.
確かに
Have you ever seen the man on the side?
副面の男は見たことありますか?
No.
ないです
There isn't.
ないよね
You have very white skin.
すごい肌白いよね
Why is your skin so white?
なんでそんな肌白いの?
I don't want to get sunburned.
日焼けしたくない
日焼けしたくないんだよ
So, outdoors rather than indoors.
じゃあ、インドアよりアウトドア
indoors rather than outdoors.
アウトドアよりインドア
It's totally outdoor.
全然アウトドアです
Is it outdoors at all?
全然アウトドアなの?
Where do you go?
どこに行ったりする?
A cafe or something.
カフェとか
Ah, a cafe.
あ、カフェね
When are your days off?
休みの日は?
What do you do to spend your time?
何 して過ごすの?
I'm sleeping.
寝てます
Are you sleeping?
寝てたり?
So, if I want to go somewhere, I'll go to a cafe.
じゃあ、どこか行こうと思ったらカフェ行ったりするんだ
nice.
いいね
So what are you doing?
それじゃあ何してるんすか?
what?
何?
It kind of makes me laugh.
なんか、笑う
student?
学生?
Not.
じゃない
Are you working?
働いてるの?
what are you doing?
何してるの?
The one who can't say it?
言えないやつ?
Can you say it?
言 えるやつ?
An idol?
アイドルとか?
i don't know.
知らない
how?
どうやって?
Why don't you tell me?
なんで言わないの?
It's a secret.
内緒なのね
Do you mean you don't want to say it?
言いたくないってこと?
No, it's fine.
いや、いいのよ
Don't say that.
そんな、言わなくて
Why don't you tell me?
なんで言わないの?
No, I'm working.
いや、働いてるね
She's a mysterious beauty.
謎の多い美女ってことで
You laugh a lot.
すごいよく笑うね
That's so interesting.
そんな、面白い
You just need to get used to it.
お前、 ちょっと慣れてもらって
Do you have a girlfriend yet?
もう彼女はいますか?
now.
今
Ah, there it is.
あ、いるんだ
How long have you been together?
どのくらい付き合ったの?
1 month.
1ヶ月
Isn't it so refreshing?
ほやほやじゃないですか?
Which way is that?
それは、どっちから?
Where did you come from?
ど っち から来たの?
From the other side.
向こうから
Now, lovey dovey?
今じゃあ、ラブラブ?
It doesn't matter.
どうでもない
usually.
普通
Did you have sex or something?
エッチとかしたの?
I'll do Danbury.
ダンバリーするね
I know.
知ってるな
You know.
知ってるね
So, how many people have you had sex with so far?
じゃあ、何人くらいで今まで エッチしてもらったの?
It's Danbury.
ダンバリーだよね
It's the Danbury girl.
ダンバリー少女だ
It's okay.
いいっていう
Because it feels so naive.
あんまり、 うぶな感じだからさ
Naughty, aren't you chewing?
エッチ、チューしてない?
first time.
初めて
I don't remember my first kiss.
ファーストキスの思い出がないんだ
There's no such thing.
そういうのないんだ
It will be.
なるだ
Nearby.
近くで
It'll be a while.
ちょっとなる
ちょっとなるだ
Let's chew.
チューしよう
May I?
いいですか?
Mr. Danbury.
ダンバリーさん
I'm awake.
起 きてる
what happened?
どうしたの?
Do you not like it?
嫌なの?
difficult?
難しい?
what?
何?
what happened?
どうしたの?
どう した の?
what happened?
どうしたの?